{
    "subject": "resource/Under_the_Hawthorn_Tree_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "Under the Hawthorn Tree (film) is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.947965681552887,
            "question": "Is 'Under the Hawthorn Tree' a book or a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8672077655792236,
            "question": "Name another film that is similar to 'Under the Hawthorn Tree'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8387005925178528,
            "question": "What type of media is 'Under the Hawthorn Tree'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.766548752784729,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'Under the Hawthorn Tree'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6013194918632507,
            "question": "Where might you watch a film like 'Under the Hawthorn Tree'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3803790807723999,
            "question": "What year was 'Under the Hawthorn Tree' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2426762729883194,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1999940425157547,
            "question": "What are some popular film genres?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1330461949110031,
            "question": "Who are some famous directors of films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11991839110851288,
            "question": "Could you give me an example of another film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Under the Hawthorn Tree (film) is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8529_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some famous directors of films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8529_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular film genres?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8529_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common characteristics of films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8529_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8529_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8529_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8529_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8529_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8529_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8529_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8529_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8529_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8529_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8529_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide various details about \"Under the Hawthorn Tree\" as a film, including its director, runtime, and plot summary. Therefore, it supports that \"Under the Hawthorn Tree (film) is a type of Film.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}